Nepal Church History Project Archives
Yale University Divinity School Library
- A - Church in Nepal, Series I
  - A07 Bible Trainings for Nepalis
    - A 07 11 01 New Theological College, Dehra Dun (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - A 07 12 01 Kathmandu Bible College (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - A 07 13 01 Life Bible Institute, Kathmandu (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - A 07 14 01 Nepal Bible College, Kathmandu (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - A 07 15 01 NBI / NBA (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - A 07 16 01 Nepali Bible School, Gorakhpur (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - A 07 17 01 Nepal Theological Seminary, P.O. Box 3535, Kathmandu / Nepal Ebenezer Bible College (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - A 07 18 01 Nepal Theological Seminary, P.O. Box 3388, Kathmandu (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - A 07 19 01 Presbyterian Theological Seminary, Dehra Dun (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - A 07 20 01 Short Term Bible Schools, INF Assisted, Pokhara (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - A 07 21 01 Short Term Bible Schools, UMN Assisted (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - A 07 22 01 Southern Asia Bible College (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - A 07 23 01 Living Word Center (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - A 07 24 01 Himalayan Ezra Institute (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - A08: Special Events, Conferences, and Evangelistic Campaigns in Nepal
    - A 08 01 01 Christmas Festival, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - A 08 02 01 East Nepal Evangelism 2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - A 08 03 01 Good News Festival, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - A 08 04 01 Nepali Pastors & Leaders Conferences, 1985 & 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - A 08 05 01 Lesslie Newbigin (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - A 08 06 01 Luis Palau Crusade, Kathmandu, Easter 1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - A 08 07 01 Vann Outreach Ministries Crusade, April 1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - A 08 08 01 Nepal AD 2000 Congress Of Evangelism, Kathmandu, October 1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - A 08 09 01 Prayer & Spiritual Warfare Conference, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - A 08 10 01 Gospel Campaign 2000, Mid & Far Western Nepal (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - A 08 11 01 Jesus Calls Campaign (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - A 08 12 01 Global Mission & Christian Workers' Conference '95 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - A 08 13 01 Christmas Good News Festival, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - A 08 14 01 Countdown 2000 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - A09: Miscellaneous Reports and Organizations Reporting on Nepal
    - A 09 01 01 Asia Link / Asia Prayer Link / Tribes And Nations Outreach (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - A 09 02 01 Blessings International (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - A 09 03 01 Christian Medical Association (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - A 09 04 01 Church Of North India (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - A 09 05 01 Evangelical Fellowship Of Asia (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - A 09 06 01 Himalayan Mission, Inc. (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - A 09 07 01 International Congress On World Evangelization, Lausanne, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - A 09 08 01 Let Asia Hear / Let Asia Speak (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - A 09 09 01 MARC (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - A 09 10 01 Prayer Fellowship For South Asia (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - A 09 10 01 Prayer Fellowship For South Asia (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - A 09 11 01 South Asia Concern (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - A 09 12 01 Voice Of The Martyrs, Inc. (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - A 09 13 01 Christian Information Network (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - A 09 14 01 Sure Destiny (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - A 09 15 01 Lydia Fellowship (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - A10: Nepali Christian Literature / Media Development
    - A 10 01 01 Miscellaneous Christian Literature Development (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - A 10 02 01 Christian Literature - Correspondence, etc. - 1954-1963 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - A 10 02 02 Christian Literature - Correspondence, etc. - 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - A 10 02 03 Christian Literature - Correspondence, etc. - 1966-1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - A 10 03 01 Communications Committee, 1970-1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - A 10 03 02 Communications Committee, 1981-1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - A 10 03 03 Communications Committee, 1986-1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - A 10 04 01 Christian Arts Association Nepal (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - A 10 05 01 Christian Media Nepal (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - A 10 06 01 Himalayan Evangel (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - A 10 07 01 Himalayan Mission Nepali Literature Committee, WEC (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - A 10 08 01 Jonathan Lindell (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - A 10 09 01 Nepali Bible (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - A 10 10 01 Nepali Hymnal (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - A 10 11 01 NISS / JPP - Darjeeling (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - A 10 12 01 Radio - FEBC, FEBA, TWR (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - A 10 13 01 Shanti Book Stall, Kathmandu (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - A 10 14 01 Vijay Press & Jill James & Pat Cook Prayer Letters (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - A11: Persecution, the Law, and Religious Freedom in Nepal
    Scope and Contents
    Includes specific court cases.
    - A 11 01 01 Nepali Law & Religious Freedom (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - A 11 02 01 Persecution & Various Arrests - Up To 1990 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - A 11 02 02 Persecution & Various Arrests - 1991- (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - A 11 03 01 Rising Nepal & Other Articles Re Religious Freedom etc. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - A 11 04 01 Tansen Arrest, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - A12: Transcripts of Interviews with Missionaries
    - A 12 01 01 Interviews With Missionaries - General (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - A 12 01 02 Allinger, Beth (WEC) (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - A 12 01 03 Anderson, Dr. Winifred (Sandy) (ZBMM/BMMF) (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - A 12 01 04 Bailey, Betty (INF) (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - A 12 01 05 Beckdahl, Rev. & Mrs. Sam (AG) (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - A 12 01 06 Best, Barbara (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - A 12 01 07 Block, John (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - A 12 01 08 Brodie, James (COS) (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - A 12 01 09 Broomhall, Paul (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - A 12 01 10 Caughley, Kathline (SIL) (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - A 12 01 11 Crane, Elaine (WEC) (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - A 12 01 12 Dick, Dr. James (COS) (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - A 12 01 13 Dodson, Dr. Pam (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - A 12 01 14 Finsas, Barbara (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - A 12 01 15 Franklin, Elizabeth (RBMU) (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - A 12 01 16 Friedericks, Carl & Betty (UMN) (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - A 12 01 17 Gilruth, Agnes (Gorakhpur Nurseries) (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - A 12 01 18 Hawker, Dr. Beryl (NEB) (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - A 12 01 19 James, Jill (Cook) (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - A 12 01 20 Lindell, Evey (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - A 12 01 21 McBurney, Amy (RBMU) (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - A 12 01 22 McCabe, Andrew (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - A 12 01 23 McCabe, George (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - A 12 01 24 Meincke, Ellen (NEB) (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - A 12 01 25 Moules, Iris (WEC) (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - A 12 01 26 Norrish, Col. Alan (BMMF) (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - A 12 01 27 Oliver, Ernest (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - A 12 01 28 Owen, Margaret (INF) (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - A 12 01 29 Pedley, Betty (Leprosy Mission) (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - A 12 01 30 Roche, Mr. & Mrs. Denis (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - A 12 01 31 Sanders, Dr. Keith (RBMU) (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - A 12 01 32 Scott-Brown, Dr. Graham (INF) (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - A 12 01 33 Scourfield, Tegwen (NEB) (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - A 12 01 34 Skjervheim, Ingeborg (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - A 12 01 36 Stephens, Irene (RBMU) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - A 12 01 37 Thompson, Mary (NEB) (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - A 12 01 38 Turner, Dr. Gerald (NEB) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - A 12 01 39 Verwer, George (OM) (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - A 12 01 40 Vickers, Nora (RBMU/UMN) (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - A 12 01 41 Wall, Stanley & Betty (NEB) (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - A 12 01 42 Walther, Grace and Lennox, Mary (AG) (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - A 12 01 43 Strong, Drs. Patricia & Trevor (RBMU) (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - A 12 01 44 Morris, Dr. Wilfrid H. (WEC) (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - A 12 01 45 Young, Dr. Katherine (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - A 12 01 46 Norman, Beryl (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - A 12 01 47 Baird, Jean (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - A13: Maps
    - A 13 01 01 Maps Of Nepal (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - A 13 02 01 Maps Of India, Bhutan, Burma (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - A 13 03 01 Maps Re Church / Mission (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - A14: Nepal Church History Project Administrative Papers
    - General (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - NCHP Committee Minutes (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Finance Reports (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Church History and Oral History Research Methods (Box 17, Folder 9)
- B - Diaspora, Series II
  - B01: Himalaya-Wide and Global Groups
    - B 01 01 01 Himalaya 2000 Movement & HIM-COE (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - B 01 01 02 HIM-COE '98 - General (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - B 01 01 03 HIM-COE '98 - Correspondence With Missionaries (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - B 01 01 04 HIM-COE '98 - Testimonies From Pioneer Missionaries (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - B 01 01 05 HIM-MEET, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - B 01 02 01 Prayer Movements Including Himali Prayer Fellowship (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - B 01 02 02 Prayer For Nepal (Global Network) (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - B 01 03 01 Himalayan Ministries - General (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - B 01 03 02 Himalayan Ministries - Prayer Letter, etc. (mainly Cindy Perry) (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - B 01 03 03 Himalayan Ministries – Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - B 01 03 04 Himalayan Ministries – Official Documents (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - B 01 03 05 Himalayan Ministries – Donors (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - B 01 03 06 Himalayan Ministries – Confidential (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - B 01 04 01 Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - B 01 05 01 Background Material (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - B 01 06 01 Christian Organisations / Missions Outside Nepal – General (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - B 01 06 02 Priscilla Centre (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - B 01 06 03 Go Fest Shillong (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - B 01 06 04 Mayel Lyang Mission (MLM) (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - B 01 06 05 Ron's Music & Youth On Fire & Four Corner Gurkha Mission (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - B 01 06 06 Shalom Ministries / Satish Chettri (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - B02: Eastern Himalayas
    - B 02 01: North Bengal, particularly Darjeeling District
      - B 02 01 01 Beginnings Of Christian Work, Darjeeling, Including Union Church (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - B 02 01 02 Church of Scotland (Box 27, Folder 2,3)
      - B 02 01 03 Missionaries - Eastern Himalayan Church (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - B 02 01 04 Nepali Pastors / Catechists - EHC, DDC (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - B 02 01 05 Individual Churches - EHC, DDC (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - B 02 01 06 General Interest / Special Activities - EHC, DDC (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - B 02 01 07 Miscellaneous - Kalimpong & Darjeeling (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - B 02 01 08 Swedish Baptist /Pentecostal - Pedong / Algarah (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - B 02 01 09 B. K. Biswas / Masih Mandali (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - B 02 01 10 S. Sodemba / Himalaya Crusade (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - B 02 01 11 Himalayan Free Church (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - B 02 01 12 S. K. Moral - Medical Ambassadors (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - B 02 01 13 Presbyterian Free Church & Himalayan Evangelical Fellowship (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - B 02 01 14 El Shaddai, Kalimpong (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - B 02 01 15 Darjeeling Background Material (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - B 02 01 16 Outlines, etc. (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - B 02 01 17 Duars - Jalpaiguri - Cooch Bihar (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Jalpaiguri Church Profiles (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - B 02 02: Sikkim
      - B 02 02 01 General (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - B 02 02 02 Finnish Mission & Scandinavian Alliance Mission (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - B 02 02 03 Eastern Himalayan Mission (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - B 02 02 04 Non-DDC (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - B 02 02 05 FECAI & Sikkim AD2000 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - B 02 02 06 Background Material (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - B 02 03: Bhutan
      - B 02 03 01 Outlines, etc. (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - B 02 03 01 Outlines, etc. (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - B 02 03 02 Carey's Bootan Mission (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - B 02 03 03 Bhutan Churches (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - B 02 03 03 Bhutan Churches (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - B 02 03 04 Bhutan Prayer News & Confidential Reports (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - B 02 03 04 Bhutan Prayer News & Confidential Reports (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - B 02 03 05 Background Material (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - B 02 04: Wider India
      - B 02 04 01 North-East India (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - B 02 04 02 North-West India (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - B 02 04 03 North India Plains (South Of Nepal) (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - B 02 04 04 Urban India (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - B 02 04 05 Assam (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - B 02 04 07 Manipur (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - B 02 04 08 Mizoram (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - B 02 04 09 Nagaland (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - B 02 04 10 Shillong / Meghalaya (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - B 02 04 11 Tripura (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - B 02 04 12 Background - North-East India (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - B 02 04 13 Background - North-West India (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - B 02 04 14 Background - North India Plains (South of Nepal) (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - B 02 04 15 Background - Urban India (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - B 02 04 16 Background - Nepalis in India (General & Political) (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - B 02 04 17 Background - India Census Statistics (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - B 02 04 18 Outlines, etc. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - B 03 Wider Nepali Diaspora
    - B 03 01: Myanmar
      - B 03 01 01 General (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - B 03 01 02 Gurkhali Christians (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - B 03 01 03 Background Material (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - B 03 02: Gurkha Regiments
      - B 03 02 01 Gurkha Christians - General (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - B 03 02 02 Gurkha Christians - Confidential (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - B 03 02 03 Jim & May Kirk, Nepali Letters, Testimonies, etc. (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - B 03 02 04 Comments/Corrections To Gurkha Chapter of C. Perry's PhD Thesis (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - B 03 03: Tibet
      - B 03 03 01 Christian Ministry (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - B 03 03 01 Christian Ministry (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - B 03 03 02 Hester Withey (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - B 03 03 02 Hester Withey (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - B 03 04: Other Countries
      - B 03 04 01 General (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - B 03 04 02 Korea (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - B 03 04 03 Malaysia & Singapore (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - B 03 04 04 North America (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - B 03 04 05 Persian Gulf (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - B 03 04 06 Philippines (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - B 03 04 07 Russia & Central Asia (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - B 03 04 08 Taiwan (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - B 03 04 09 Thailand (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - B 03 04 10 Background - Colonies (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - B 03 04 11 Background - Middle East & Arabia (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - B 04 General (Non-Church) Information on Nepalis in India and Abroad
    - B 04 01 01 Nepal & Nepalis - General Background (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - B 04 02 01 Nepali Migration - General (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - B 04 02 02 Nepali Migration - Nepali Scholars (Box 23, Folder 8)
- C - Audio Visual Nepali Language or Church Related Media Collection, Series III
  - C 01 Audio Media
    Includes tapes of interviews. See transcripts at A12
    - C 01 01 01 Interviews, Testimonies & Recollections On Audio Cassettes (Standard size) (Box 29)
    - C 01 01 02 Music & Songs On Audio Cassettes (Standard size) (Box 30)
    - C 01 02 01 Interviews, Testimonies & Recollections On Microcassettes (Box 30)
    - C01 03 01 Reel-to-Reel Tapes (Box 31)
  - C 02 Visual Media
    - C 02 01 01 Videos (VHS) (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - C 02 02 01 CD-ROMs (Box 31)
    - C 02 03 01 DVDs / VCDs (Box 31)
- D - Nepali Christian Literature Collection, Series IV
  - D 01 Nepali-Language Christian Literature Published in India
    - D 01 01 01 Bible Society, India (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - D 01 02 01 Darjeeling Diocese Publications (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - D 01 03 01 East Himalayan Lit. and Miscellaneous Darjeeling (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - D 01 04 01 El Shaddai (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - D 01 05 01 Evangelical Literature Depot, Calcutta (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - D 01 06 01 Kitty Harbord and NBF (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - D 01 07 01 Maranatha Revival Church (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - D 01 08 01 Miscellaneous (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - D 01 09 01 Operation Mobilization (Masihi Sahitya Sanstha) (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - D 01 10 01 Scripture Gift Mission (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - D 01 11 01 Scripture Union (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - D 01 12 01 Shillong (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - D 01 13 01 WEC (Worldwide Evangelization Crusade) (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - D 01 14 01 World Mission Prayer League / Mirik Press (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - D 01 15 01 Himali Prakashan (Box 33, Folder 1, 2)
    - D 01 016 01 Jiwan Jyoti Press (Box 33, Folder 3, 4)
    - D 01 17 01 NISS (Nepali Isai Sahitya Sangha) (Box 35, Folder 1-3)
    - D 01 17 01 NISS (Nepali Isai Sahitya Sangha) (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - D 01 18 01 Vijay Press (Box 36, Folder 2, 3)
  - D 02 Nepali-Language Christian Literature Published in Nepal
    - D 02 01 01 CAAN (Christian Arts Association Nepal) (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - D 02 02 01 Gyaneshwar Church (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - D 02 03 01 International Correspondence Institute (AOG) (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - D 02 04 01 Jiwan Marga Sahitya Prakashan (D. Cloud) (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - D 02 05 01 Jonathan Book Store (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - D 02 06 01 Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 3-4)
    - D 02 07 01 NBCBS (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - D 02 08 01 Nepal Khristiyan Bal Shikchaa Sangati (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - D 02 09 01 Nepal Khristiya Sangati (NCF) (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - D 02 10 01 Nepal Every Home Concern (NEHC) (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - D 02 11 01 Nepal Prayer Fellowship (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - D 02 12 01 Nepal Prison Fellowship (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - D 02 13 01 Patan Book House (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - D 02 14 01 Ramghat Church (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - D 02 15 01 Roman Catholic Publications (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - D 02 16 01 Adon Rongong (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - D 02 17 01 Samdan (Box 38, Folder 1, 2)
    - D 02 18 01 Sarikar Prakashan (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - D 02 19 01 Satya Bato Prakshan (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - D 02 20 01 Scripture Union, Nepal (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - D 02 21 01 Shubha Khabar Prakashan (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - D 02 22 01 Teach Ministries (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - D 02 23 01 UMN (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - D 02 24 01 Bible Society in Nepal (Box 39, Folder 1-4)
    - D 02 25 01 Gospel for Asia & Bodhartha Prakashan (Box 39, Folder 5, 6)
    - D 02 25 01 Gospel for Asia & Bodhartha Prakashan (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - D 02 26 01 Bachan Prakashan (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - D 02 06 01 Oversize (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - D 03 Christian Literature in Other Languages
    - D 03 01 01 Hindi (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - D 03 02 01 Lepsha (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - D 03 03 01 Maithili (Box 36, Folder 5)
- E - Nepali Christian Magazines, Series V
  - E 01 General
    - E 01 01 01 General information about Nepali-language Christian magazines (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - E 02 Miscellaneous Nepali-Language Christian Magazines
    - E 02 01 01 Published in Darjeeling (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - E 02 02 01 Published in Nepal (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - E 02 03 01 Published in Sikkim (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - E 03 Individual Nepali-Language Christian Magazines
    - E 03 01 01 Athmik Yatra (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - E 03 02 01 Be-Get (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - E 03 03 01 Bhetghat - Magazine (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - E 03 03 02 Bhetghat - Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - E 03 04 01 Bodhartha (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - E 03 05 01 Darjeeling CNI Magazines - Eastern Himalayan Church News (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - E 03 05 02 Darjeeling CNI Magazines - Darjeeling Diocesan Church News (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - E 03 05 03 Darjeeling CNI Magazines - Outreach (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - E 03 06 01 Diyo (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - E 03 07 01 Hera, Tee Nayan Bhaisakey (Himali Prakashan) (Box 41, Folder 3, 4)
    - E 03 08 01 Himalayan Evangel (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - E 03 09 01 Kanchan (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - E 03 10 04 Bachan-Sandarabh / Bachan Sandarabhma / Kiran (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - E 03 11 01 Prakaska Pailaharu (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - E 03 12 01 Rajdoot - Magazine (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - E 03 12 01 Rajdoot - Correspondence (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - E 03 13 01 Sangati (Box 42, Folder 3, 4)
    - E 03 14 01 The Voice of Calvary - Magazine (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - E 03 15 01 Aatmik Ekta (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - E 04 Individual Christian Magazines in Other Languages
    - Voice of Bhakti (Box 42, Folder 7)
- F - Church Survey, Series VI
  Items related to September-December 1987 and 1992 surveys. Includes survey forms, reports, etc.
  - F 01 01 01 Survey of the Church in Nepal - 1987 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - F 02 01 01 Survey of the Church in Nepal - 1992 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- G - Photograph Collection, Series VII
  See listing at repository. More than 480 photographs from the collection have been digitized.
  - G 01 The Nepali Church Outside Nepal Prior to 1990
    - G 01 01 01 Early Pioneers (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - G 01 02 01 Nepal Bible Fellowship (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - G 01 03 01 Bible Translation (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - G 01 04 01 Uttar Pradesh - Assemblies of God (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - G 01 05 01 Nautanwa - ZBMM (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - G 01 05 02 Nautanwa - WEC (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - G 01 05 03 Nautanwa - NEB (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - G 01 06 01 Raxaul - RBMU (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - G 01 07 01 Shillong / Assam - NEB / WEC (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - G 01 08 01 Darjeeling District - Eastern Himalayan Church (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - G 01 08 02 Darjeeling District - Eastern Himalayan Mission (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - G 01 08 03 Darjeeling District - WEC (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - G 01 08 04 Darjeeling District - NEB (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - G 01 08 05 Darjeeling District - Presbyterian Free Church (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - G 01 08 06 Darjeeling District - Darjeeling Hills Bible School (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - G 01 08 07 Darjeeling District - Miscellaneous (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - G 01 09 01 Darjeeling, Sikkim, Bhutan - Finnish Free Mission (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - G 01 10 01 Kalimpong - Elizabeth Franklin Team (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - G 01 10 02 Kalimpong - Dr. Graham's HOmes (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - G 01 10 03 Kalimpong - Churches (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - G 01 10 04 Kalimpong - Orphanages (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - G 01 11 01 Sikkim - Eastern Himalayan Church (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - G 01 11 02 Sikkim - Himanchal Kristiya Sangati (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - G 01 12 01 Calcutta (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - G 01 03 01 North-East India - Megalaya (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - G 01 13 02 North-East India - Nagaland (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - G 01 13 03 North-East India - Manipur (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - G 01 14 01 Bhutan - Estern Himalayan Church (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - G 01 14 02 Bhutan - Norwegian Santal Mission (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - G 01 15 01 Gurkha Soldiers (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - G 02 The Church Inside Nepal
    - G 02 01 01 Nepal Christian Fellowship (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - G 02 02 01 Persecution (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - G 02 03 01 Para-Church Organizations - Nepal Every Home Concern (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - G 02 03 02 Para-Church Organizations - Campus Crusade (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - G 02 03 03 Para-Church Organizations - Assemblies of God, Discipleship Training Centre (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - G 02 03 04 Para-Church Organizations -Nepal Prayer Fellowship (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - G 02 03 05 Para-Church Organizations - Nepal Bible Ashram (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - G 02 03 06 Para-Church Organizations - Gospel Recordings (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - G 02 03 07 Para-Church Organizations - Bal Sangati (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - G 02 03 08 Para-Church Organizations - Gospel for Asia (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - G 02 03 09 Para-Church Organizations - Prison Fellowship (Box 44, Folder 11)